I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky….
I believe in tomorrow if we try, I… Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one dream.
Come on, let's go everybody.
Oh, we share the good times.
We share the good times.
Maybe, maybe, oh we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see or to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought up by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
No matter what, I'll
try no matter how high.
So let us go beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world? No!
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased?
From the top we go on straight and wild!
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart!
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I Share
the laundry, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now!
I look up to the stars
And reach for the sky
No matter what I'll
try no matter how high!
So let us go Beyond far and wide I
believe in tomorrow If we try high
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah I know that you are there Just on the
other side Wait there
for me Soon it will be
you and I Then let us
go Beyond far and wide
I believe in the one world If we try high
Oh, we share the music
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one world
Hey, Devil, I mean, handsome What do you
think's taking the Straw Hat so long?
Pirates and Marines were
fighting like crazy.
Hope they didn't get caught in that?
Stay sharp!
With all of those idiots
running wild all over Sabo Odi.
Who knows if their ship will be safe?
That's why we've got to
guard it with our very lives.
Until the coding craftsman shows up
and takes over, don't budge and itch.
You got that, Rosie Life Riders?
Roger, Captain Handsome!
What do you mean you haven't caught them?
Admiral Kizaru is
pursuing them as we speak,
so I'm sure it's only a matter of
time until they're captured, ma 'am.
You bunch of useless dogs!
Not only did you allow them
to do this to my father
and brother you also let
every last one Of our
slaves escape and yet i
must save my contempt for
the pirates who made a
mockery of Our bloodline when
you catch those heathens
i'll show them a true
living hell until they beg
for Death on their knees i
have a bad feeling about
this all of a sudden i sure
hope luffy chin and his
friends are okay out there.
Come on, Kuma, don't say stuff like that!
You're just gonna stress everybody out!
Yeah, but...
You...
The Straw Hats are tough, you know that.
There's nothing to worry about.
I hope you're right.
You've seen how strong that guy is!
But not stronger than an admiral.
I'm not saying that they'll lose.
But this will take more
than just strength. You?
The seas ahead will be rough for them.
Filled with waves the likes
of which have never been
seen before and yet they must
withstand them ride them?
It's quiet, but can you hear it?
Little by little the tides are
changing and the world with them.
After being ejected from
Sabo Head, Monkey D.
Luffy found himself on
a very unique journey.
Zoro! Nami!
I'm sorry! Usam!
Soji Chopper!
Robin! Franky! Brooke! Everybody!
Where did you go?
You guys can't be dead!
Dammit there was nothing I could do that
stupid warlord is gonna pay for this.
I hate this it sucks how
far am I gonna fly anyway?
Oh that could be good
news maybe everyone didn't
disappear they're just
flying around like me.
Although three days of
this sure will be boring
if I fall in the ocean
that'll be the end of me.
I'm so hungry, too. Screw this.
I'm going to sleep.
On and on he soared through starry skies.
Then, at long last...
I'm alive.
I know what happened.
But I don't think my rubber
power saved me this time.
Also, what's this bear paw
looking thing doing on the ground?
If everyone else had a landing like this?
They might be okay.
Oh well, gotta get back!
Where am I?
And which way does the Sabaody
Archipelago go from here?
Wait a sec!
I have my Vibra card, of course.
Alright, good thing everyone got one, huh?
Let's go.
Easy, follow the card.
We'll be back together in no time.
That way.
Everyone, start running
and look after yourselves.
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
Just go! Get out of there!
We can figure out a plan once we're safe!
Run!
Why the hell am I so weak?
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
Actually, that didn't hurt that bad.
That rock's still in the way.
No doubt about it.
The card's pointing in that direction.
Fine.
Giant pistol!
Man, I can't do it.
I'm all out of power.
I need food. Saji!
Who am I kidding?
I know he's not here.
Thanks for all the food, buddy.
Ugh, that really brings me back.
Grandpa Garp used to throw me in the
jungle all the time when I was a kid.
Actually, that kind of sucked.
Hey, aren't these laughing mushrooms?
Perfect, this is just
what I need right now.
Yeah, now I'm having fun,
even though I'm all alone.
Ooh, these look weird. Let's try them.
Now I'm mad!
Laughing mushrooms, laughing mushrooms.
Hey, look, there's more over here.
Oh, crying mushroom.
Calm down.
I'm right here, Sweet Pea.
What do you make of it?
Huh?
Rather puzzling, isn't it?
Oh, this is terrible.
I think this is a human.
Is she from the village?
I don't know.
There are so many mushrooms growing
out of her body, I can't even tell.
Hmm.
Aha!
Ah, look here.
This must be why she ate these.
A parasitic mushroom.
When you eat one, a whole sea of
them pop up all over your body.
We have to do something.
Or these mushrooms will sap away
all of her strength and she'll die.
Then make haste before all is lost.
Off Alondra, carry her to
the village and quickly.
Okay.
Stay strong, small one.
We will find aid. Let's hope.
We have an emergency!
Hey!
Down in front!
I can't see!
Goodness! Mushrooms! What happened?
I haven't seen that girl
in the village before.
Have you?
No, not me.
Hey, who is that?
With all those mushrooms,
it's hard to tell.
Any idea where she came
from? Is she alive?
She ate a parasitic mushroom, and now
they're growing all over her body.
Belladonna, what do
you think we should do?
You can pull them off, but
we have to get them all.
Be thorough. Huh?
They come off?
Oh, wow.
But some of the bases are still stuck.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of them later.
Just keep pulling.
She's so odd.
Are you sure that this was wise?
Huh?
Uh.
Oh, no!
I'm on fire! Put me out!
Hold on.
Belladonna, what are you doing?
This is the only way to
keep them from growing back.
Still, it seems a bit excessive.
She passed out again.
Well, that's interesting.
It seems she was covered in injuries
before she was covered in mushrooms.
She was?
She must have gone through
quite the terrible battle.
We need to treat her wounds.
Do me a favor, Margaret.
Take her down to the river
and give her a good bath.
Uh, yes.
Yes, of course.
Well, it appears that she's
not from the village after all.
How strange. Yes. Huh?
Hold on. What is this?
It's something wrong.
We've been remiss in our
mushroom picking duties.
There's one between our legs
that we failed to catch.
How careless of us.
Huh, you're right.
But this one seems different
than the others, doesn't it?
It has such a strange shape.
It won't come off but why hey what's going
on it's stretching what is a mushroom?
That's enough stop gawking ladies
they aren't putting on a show for you!
If we leave so do you hey look that isn't
normal is it it's strange
she's sort of rugged.
Not very well endowed, either.
It's no use.
Oh, my. What's this?
Is something wrong?
Oh, hello, Granny Nyon.
There's a mushroom
growing on this girl that
won't come off no matter how hard we try.
Oh, goodness.
But who is she?
Oh, no! Huh?
This person is a...
It's a man! A man!
I've never seen a man before.
Whatever shall I do?
Here lies the maiden
island of Amazon Lily,
inhabited by a tribe of female
warriors known as the Kuja.
Woe be to the man who dreams of this
land And woe be to the man who seeks
it For if they shall ever set foot
upon its soil Death surely awaits them
This is the all-female land of Amazon Lily
where men dare not tread
on occasion the women
who live here will leave
the island and return
with child but oddly enough they only seem
to give birth to girls here a thick jungle
surrounds a mountain that
stretches towards the
sky nestled inside its rocky exterior is a
fortress-like village that
houses the entire nation
That was a real disaster.
Step right up.
We got seeking, so get
it while it's fresh.
That looks yummy, and it'll make
your skin nice and soft too.
Fresh-picked fruit from
the jungle straight to you!
Fun-loving and hard-working, no job
is too challenging for these women.
Hey, Lock what I got!
That'll be perfect.
Just set it down right there.
Sure thing!
Raised from birth as warriors,
they are as brave and
adventurous as any man,
but have an undeniable grace about them.
Their seclusion has also given
them an air of innocence.
Here in this paradise, there
is no need for men at all.
Because these women, above
all else, are strong.
Here are today's odds.
A thousand gold on puppy.
Fifteen hundred on candy.
In this land,
strength is beauty, and tempting
though its lovely sights may be,
any man foolish enough to gaze upon these
warriors will not live to tell the tale.
The man is awake!
Let me see, let me see!
Okay, we'll take turns!
He's moving around.
Look at his chest.
It's so flat.
Awfully chiseled looking isn't he?
Rather underwhelming.
I'd say.
And his hair's so shaggy.
It seems like he was sleeping forever.
But I heard he was eating
while he was asleep.
Is that a man?
Thing.
What is it that men eat anyway?
Just raw meat.
I get the feeling this
one will eat anything.
What's going on?
It sure is noisy.
Oh, he can talk!
Hey, hold on. Where am I?
And what the heck was I
doing before I passed out?
That's right.
We got split up and I
landed someplace weird.
Everyone, he's saying something.
I remember eating some
mushrooms, but after that...
Oh, my hat's missing!
Hey!
There it is!
Give it back, you jerk!
Weird!
Our bodies can't do that!
Yeah!
That's better!
Oh, wow!
That means men can stretch their
arms! Interesting! Very good!
Most intriguing indeed!
Man, would you tell us your name, please?
Huh?
Oh, I'm Luffy!
Whoa!
That's weird, I'm naked!
We know!
It's kind of breezy in here.
Anybody know where my stuff went?
Men are slow-witted,
and they cover their heads first
even if their bodies are exposed.
Um, pardon me for asking, but, uh...
Before you get dressed,
could you please tell us what's in that
little bag that's in
between your legs there?
Bag?
Come on, you don't know what those are?
What a weirdo.
These are my family jewels.
They're jewels?
So what are these jewels?
It's my treasure.
That's why I always gotta keep them safe.
Family jewels?
I wish I had some too!
Then could you please take them out?
We'd just like to hold them for a second.
Are you nuts?
You'll kill me!
Not a chance!
Might as well get dressed, then.
Your clothes are all
torn when we found you,
so I made some new ones
that are just like them.
Wow!
Hey, thanks a lot!
That was real nice, and we
don't even know each other.
So flowery.
The vest says I'm serious,
but the frilsy, I'm cute.
His enemies will shake with
fear and jealousy alike.
You're a genius, Margaret.
Oh, look, he's so happy he's shaking.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Are you trying to make fun of me? Huh?
Prepare to attack what
what a vicious temper
he shows his true nature
you see my sisters even
after we save his life
he turns on us growling
and snapping like the
beast he is his temperament
is indeed savage his
words and actions lack any
elegance whatsoever we
are incompatible with him
and every man even so
key killer his offense
towards us is truly minor
we need not kill him Hey,
before you guys shoot me, just a
second ago you said you saved my life.
What happened?
I don't even know.
You ate a bunch of parasitic
mushrooms and collapsed.
Then you were found and
brought here by these ladies.
Okay, that's what happened.
In that case, thanks a lot.
Sorry for flipping out and
complaining about the clothes.
Just don't shoot me.
Your apologies are meaningless.
This is Amazon Lily, female empire.
All men are forbidden.
And for centuries now, we have
upheld this absolute rule.
You shall die like every man
on this island before you.
No guys, huh?
Now that we know your true nature,
we have no sympathy for you.
Wow, you're right.
Now that I look, you are all girls.
Man, what a crazy country.
And still you prattle
on, you ignorant worm!
He's not so bad.
Do we gotta kill him?
Aphalandra!
The snake princess will soon return.
How do you think she will feel?
She would never approve of this situation.
You will also be charged with the crime
of bringing a man into the village.
Margaret.
Sweet Peep.
Aphalandra.
I'm doing this for your sake.
This incident?
...must be kept secret.
Hold on a sec!
Can't you just let me go? My friends!
They're waiting for me on Sabahori!
And I promised I would meet them there!
Shoot him!
Look up there!
He broke through the roof!
Don't let him escape!
Ahhhhhhh!
My, my, he's a rather
nimble one, isn't he?
Opalandra!
Got it!
Oh well, I tried to save you.
He fell!
Now he's bouncing!
What should I do now?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Where's my fever card?
I had it in the pocket of
my pants before I lost them.
So, let's see.
There she is! Perfect!
I can't talk in this crowd.
I'm sorry, but there's
something I gotta ask you.
Let me go! Help!
That fiend, what does
he want with Margaret?
Go, go, go!
Hey, are you alright over
there stay away from me?
How how did you turn fat?
Are you out of your mind jumping from all
the way up there human are monsters I?
Don't know what you did
or what you were thinking,
but it's a miracle that we're still alive.
Oh, yeah
I'm not gonna do anything.
I've heard it said that all men have
some sort of dangerous cootie virus.
Is that what caused you to
grow so fat all of a sudden?
I hate to break it to you, but
I don't think cooties are real.
And the fat thing is
kind of hard to explain,
so let's just say that
yeah, all guys turn fat.
Anyway, there was something I left in
the pocket of my old pair of pants.
Do you still have it?
Yes! Yes!
Man, I was so worried!
I don't know what I would
have done if I'd lost it.
Thank you.
You're a real lifesaver.
Get your hands off me.
Stay put. You're mine.
Something was written on it,
so I kept it just in case.
Here, look.
How unusual.
It looks like it's moving.
A bunch of stuff happened,
and then all my friends went flying
through the air in different directions.
But now, with this piece of paper, I can
find my way back to them wherever they go.
They're strong, so I'm not worried.
Anyway, guess I should pay
you back for all your help.
If there's anything I
can do for you, just ask.
Oh, there is!
Could you take out your family
jewels so I can see them?
That's not even funny!
You're gonna kill me!
Just put the sword down and
leave my jewels alone, please!
These friends of yours,
who are they exactly?
Ugh, well, we're all a pirate crew.
Do you know what pirates are here?
Yes, of course I know.
In fact, the empress of this
country is a pirate as well.
Oh, really?
So, you guys have like
an all-girl pirate crew?
Are they strong?
What a foolish question only the most
elite warriors are allowed to ride
aboard the pirate ship of our empress
so yes of course they're strong
in this proud nation all of the women
look up to the snake princess her beauty
is unparalleled she's strong and noble
she's called the pirate empress boa
Hancock she and her sisters are the
protectors of this island and well truth
be told they're
our heroes oh no the
ship of the snake princess is nearly here
curses this isn't good we
must deal with the man quickly
kinkyo he jumped over the wall and disappeared
what should we do now warriors to the
jungle we will rescue
margaret then put the
man to death the snake
princess has returned